// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "How many players are there on a baseball team?",
        answer: "9",
        options: [
            "8",
            "9",
            "10",
            "11"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which country won the World Cup 2018?",
        answer: "France",
        options: [
            "England and Wales",
            "Sri Lanka",
            "India",
            "France",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which among the following team was first winner of World Cup Hockey ?",
        answer: "Pakistan",
        options: [
            "Spain",
            "France",
            "Pakistan",
            "UK",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Who is the father of the modern Commonwealth Games?",
        answer: "Melville Marks Robinson",
        options: [
            "Melville Marks Robinson",
            "Bruce Robertson",
            "Jacques Rogge",
            "Juan Antonio Samaranch",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "In which Summer Olympics, Roller Hockey was introduced for the first time as a demonstration sport?",
        answer: "1992 Summer Olympics",
        options: [
            "1992 Summer Olympics",
            "1996 Summer Olympics",
            "2000 Summer Olympics",
            "2004 Summer Olympics",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which sport’s competition is known as “Indian Wells Masters”?",
        answer: "Tennis",
        options: [
            "Football",
            "Volleyball",
            "Tennis",
            "Polo",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is Liu Shiwen famous for?",
        answer: "As a Chinese table tennis player",
        options: [
            "As a Chinese badminton player",
            " As a Chinese polo player",
            "As a Chinese tennis player",
            "As a Chinese table tennis player",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What denotes the Latin word “Sagittarii”?",
        answer: "Archers",
        options: [
            "Boxers",
            "Archers",
            "Wrestlers",
            "Golfers",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which Indian boxer won the first-ever Olympic medal in boxing?",
        answer: "Vijender Singh",
        options: [
            " Shushil Kumar",
            "Mary Kom",
            "Vijender Singh",
            "Jitender Kumar",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "In which year, hockey was introduced for the first time in the Commonwealth Games?",
        answer: "1998",
        options: [
            "1995",
            "1996",
            "1997",
            "1998",
        ]
    }
]